[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "rust?",
    "answer": "fedge",
    "tag": "rust",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-26T23:05:40.614Z",
    "category": "FOURTH"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "amk",
    "answer": "dina",
    "tag": "pap",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-26T23:06:09.875Z",
    "category": "THIRD"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "votreQuestion",
    "answer": "votreReponse",
    "tag": "votreTag",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-23T14:17:47.737Z",
    "category": "THIRD"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "1+1+1",
    "answer": "3",
    "tag": "mathimatik",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-26T22:58:31.542Z",
    "category": "THIRD"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is pair programming ?",
    "answer": "A practice to work in pair on same computer.",
    "tag": "Teamwork",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-26T23:04:40.110Z",
    "category": "FOURTH"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is pair programming ?",
    "answer": "rist.",
    "tag": "rust",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-20T14:38:45.749Z",
    "category": "FIRST"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "question?",
    "answer": "réponse",
    "tag": "tagtag",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-26T23:06:48.659Z",
    "category": "FOURTH"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is pair programming ?",
    "answer": "rist.",
    "tag": "rust",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-24T09:16:17.111Z",
    "category": "THIRD"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "question?222",
    "answer": "réponse",
    "tag": "CARTE DE TEST",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-29T20:08:35.994Z",
    "category": "SECOND"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "badis",
    "answer": "tighlit",
    "tag": "tag",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-26T23:07:07.125Z",
    "category": "SECOND"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "comment",
    "answer": "il va",
    "tag": "tagat",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-29T20:09:06.958Z",
    "category": "SECOND"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "je crée2",
    "answer": "question2",
    "tag": "TAG",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-26T23:02:03.833Z",
    "category": "THIRD"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Bonjour",
    "answer": "bonjour",
    "tag": "bjr",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-27T22:32:31.734Z",
    "category": "SECOND"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "a",
    "answer": "a",
    "tag": "a",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-29T20:08:53.701Z",
    "category": "SECOND"
  }
]